Hello everyone, in this tutorial video, we will learn how to use the historical record function.
First, in Marvelous Designer, if you want to go back to the previous operation, press Ctrl Z to go back to the previous operation.
Press Ctrl Y to go back to the previous operation.
If you want to quickly go back to the previous operation, you can click on the Library window and find the History window.
In the History window, you will see the previous operation steps.
If you click on one of the operation steps, you will return to this operation step.
The current operation steps will be the same as the previous operation steps.
The current operation steps will be displayed in orange.
If you are a virtual model who has changed the movement, you can only change the movement of the model.
You have to click on the next step to go back to the previous operation step.
If you have done other operations after going back to the previous operation step, all the previous operations will be covered.
For example, after the previous operation step,
you will see the operation steps that have been added.
But now, because we have selected the version, those operations have been covered.
If we want to save all the virtual models and costumes in the current 3D window,
we can click on the historical record 3D costume status in the upper right corner of the historical record.
When there is a 3D record in the 3D costume record box in the upper left corner,
it represents all the objects in the current 3D window.
All the objects in the current 3D window have been recorded.
It is worth noting that when we go back to the previous operation steps,
as long as we do not perform other operation steps, the later operation steps will not be covered.
For example, we go back to the previous operation steps and then click on the 3D costume record,
we can add a new 3D costume record.
Because considering what I said before,
if we do other operations after going back to the operation steps,
then the later steps will be covered.
So we can save a 3D costume record in advance.
But when we open the 3D costume record,
it will prompt you to delete the current work record.
In other words, when you open a 3D costume record,
all the historical records we saved before will be deleted.
And when we double-click to open the 3D costume record,
we will see that it actually opens a temporary project file.
Here we will see that when we double-click to open the 3D costume record,
the previous operation steps have been cleared.
Because we have added a 3D costume record before,
we can double-click to open another costume record.
This is also the same as before.
Click to confirm.
After opening it, you will see that it has now switched to the costume wearing effect under the virtual model.
In fact, the 3D costume records we saved
are all some project files in the C drive.
If we want to find these two project files,
click on the file in the upper left corner to save as a project,
you can find these two files.
After finding them, we can copy the path in these two files,
and paste these two files.
Because these two files are temporarily stored in the C drive,
so if you need them, just paste them.
So in essence,
the 3D costume record state is also a temporary way to save costume files.
That's it for this episode of the introduction of the 3D costume record function.
See you next time.
Bye bye.